Faculty Reference Collection
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Hodge, Francis P., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1393 (Box 18, Folder 68)
- Hodge, Frank, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1394 (Box 18, Folder 69)
- Hodges, Stephen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1395 (Box 18, Folder 70)
- Hoecker, Denise K., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1396 (Box 18, Folder 71)
- Hoehn, Nancy M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1397 (Box 18, Folder 72)
- Hoff, Timothy J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1398 (Box 18, Folder 73)
- Hoffmann, Erik P, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1399 (Box 18, Folder 74)
- Hoffmann, Erik P, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1400 (Box 18, Folder 75)
- Hoffman, Richard J., 1998-2001; nam_ua950.003-1401 (Box 18, Folder 76)
- Hoffman, Robert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1402 (Box 18, Folder 77)
- Hoffman, Robert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1403 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Hogan, Austin W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1404 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Hogan, Austin, ca. 1966-1987; nam_ua950.003-1405 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Hogan, Justin, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1406 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Hogan, Paul, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1407 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Holler, Leslie Ann, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1408 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Hollon, Robert E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1409 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Holmes, David, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1410 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Holsinger, Donald B., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1411 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Holstein, William K., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1412 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Holstein, William K., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1413 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Holstein, William K., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1414 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Holstein, William K., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1415 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Holstein, William K., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1416 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Holt, Linda, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1417 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Hood, Janet, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1418 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Hood, Janet, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1419 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Hoogenboom, Hilde, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1420 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Hoover, Robert C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1421 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Hope, Monica, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1422 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Hopkins, Vivian C., 1909-1990; nam_ua950.003-1423 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Hopkins, Vivian, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1424 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Hopson, Laura, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1425 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Horgen, Anne, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1426 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Horn, Margarite E., 1997; nam_ua950.003-1427 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Horne, Marcia, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1428 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Horner, Harlan Hoy, 1917-1923; nam_ua950.003-1429 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Horney, Julie, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1430 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Horney, Julie, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1431 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Horowitz, Mrs. Bernard (Helen), Undated; nam_ua950.003-1432 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Horowitz, Helen G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1433 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Horton, Heather K., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1434 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Hoskins, Ronald B, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1435 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Hotaling, Kay C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1436 (Box 19, Folder 34)
- Hotchkiss, Rollin, 1982; nam_ua950.003-1437 (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Hotelling, Charles S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1438 (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Hotopp, Matt, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1439 (Box 19, Folder 37)
- Houschen, Ellen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1440 (Box 19, Folder 38)
- Howard, Carl L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1441 (Box 19, Folder 39)
- Howard, Carolyn, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1442 (Box 19, Folder 40)
- Howell, Robert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1443 (Box 19, Folder 41)
- Howell, Robert C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1444 (Box 19, Folder 42)
- Howes, Harold, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1445 (Box 19, Folder 43)
- Howes, Harold, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1446 (Box 19, Folder 44)
- Hoyle, Norman, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1447 (Box 19, Folder 45)
- Hu, Zheng, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1448 (Box 19, Folder 46)
- Huang, Mengbing, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1449 (Box 19, Folder 47)
- Huang, Youquin, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1450 (Box 19, Folder 48)
- Hudson, Cheryl, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1451 (Box 19, Folder 49)
- Hudson, Judith, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1452 (Box 19, Folder 50)
- Hudson, Judith, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1453 (Box 19, Folder 51)
- Huffmire, Margaret Conway, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1454 (Box 19, Folder 52)
- Hughes, James W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1455 (Box 19, Folder 53)
- Hughes, Susan M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1456 (Box 19, Folder 54)
- Hughs, Richard E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1457 (Box 19, Folder 55)
- Hulstrunk, A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1458 (Box 19, Folder 56)
- Humphrey, Alex, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1459 (Box 19, Folder 57)
- Humphries, Laud, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1460 (Box 19, Folder 58)
- Hunsberger, I. Moyer, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1461 (Box 19, Folder 59)
- Hunter, Gregory Scott, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1462 (Box 19, Folder 60)
- Hunt, Harry B. III, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1463 (Box 19, Folder 61)
- Hunt, Patrick J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1464 (Box 19, Folder 62)
- Hurley, Ivan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1465 (Box 19, Folder 63)
- Hurst, Vernon T., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1466 (Box 19, Folder 64)
- Husson, William, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1467 (Box 19, Folder 65)
- Hutchins, Ruth E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1468 (Box 19, Folder 66)
- Hutchinson, David, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1469 (Box 19, Folder 67)
- Huth, Harvey, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1470 (Box 19, Folder 68)
- Huxford, Kathryn, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1471 (Box 19, Folder 69)
- Hwang, Syni-An, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1472 (Box 19, Folder 70)
- Hyde, Jonathan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1473 (Box 19, Folder 71)
- Iacobucci, Christine, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1474 (Box 19, Folder 72)
- Idleman, Peter, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1475 (Box 19, Folder 73)
- Idone, Vincent, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1476 (Box 19, Folder 74)
- Ilchman, Warren F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1477 (Box 19, Folder 75)
- Ilchman, Warren F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1478 (Box 19, Folder 76)
- Infante, Dominic A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1479 (Box 19, Folder 77)
- Ingison, Linda J., 1980; nam_ua950.003-1480 (Box 19, Folder 78)
- Ingles, Richard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1481 (Box 19, Folder 79)
- Inomata, Akira, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1482 (Box 19, Folder 80)
- Inomata, Akira, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1483 (Box 19, Folder 81)
- Ireland, Timothy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1484 (Box 19, Folder 82)
- Irving, Suzanne, 1990; nam_ua950.003-1485 (Box 19, Folder 83)
- Israel, Allen C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1486 (Box 19, Folder 84)
- Isser, Stanley J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1487 (Box 19, Folder 85)
- Istvan, Joseph A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1488 (Box 19, Folder 86)
- Ivanoff, Andre M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1489 (Box 19, Folder 87)
- Ives, Jane K., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1490 (Box 19, Folder 88)
- Iwanska, Alicja, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1491 (Box 19, Folder 89)
- Iwanska, Alicja, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1492 (Box 19, Folder 90)
- Izzard, Colin S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1493 (Box 19, Folder 91)
- Jaccard, James J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1494 (Box 19, Folder 92)
- Jaccard, James, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1495 (Box 19, Folder 93)
- Jacklet, Alice, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1496 (Box 19, Folder 94)
- Jacklet, Jon W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1497 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Jacklet, Jon W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1498 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Jacobi, Lotte, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1499 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Jacobs, Suzanne, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1500 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Jacobs, Ronald, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1501 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Jacobson, Dorothy T., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1502 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Jacobson, Dorothy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1503 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Jacobson, Trudi, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1504 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Jaeger, Robert G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1505 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Jagerson, Todd, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1506 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- James, Jasmine, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1507 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Jamison, Benton N., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1508 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Jamison, Benton, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1509 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Janecek, John, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1510 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Janesick, Valerie J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1511 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Jelinek, Mariann, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1512 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Janower, David M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1513 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Jarvenpa, Robert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1514 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Jarvis, Dave, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1515 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Jean-Baptiste, Rachel, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1516 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Jefferson, Roslyn, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1517 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Jeffries, Leonard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1518 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Jenkins, Joe W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1519 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Jenkins, Joe W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1520 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Jenks, David W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1521 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Jennings, Edward M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1522 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Jennings, Edward M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1523 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Jennings, John W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1524 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Jerison, Michael, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1525 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Jerison, Michael, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1526 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Jerum, Kathryn J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1527 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Jewett, Alice B., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1528 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Jiusto, James E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1529 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Jiusto, James, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1530 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Johnpoll, Bernard K., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1531 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Johnpoll, Bernard K., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1532 (Box 20, Folder 36)
- Johnson, Jacqueline, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1533 (Box 20, Folder 37)
- Johnson, Judith, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1534 (Box 20, Folder 38)
- Johnson, Kecia, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1535 (Box 20, Folder 39)
- Johnson, Mauritz, 1955-1968; nam_ua950.003-1536 (Box 20, Folder 40)
- Johnson, Mauritz, Jr., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1537 (Box 20, Folder 41)
- Johnson, Mary T., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1538 (Box 20, Folder 42)
- Johnson, Pamela F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1539 (Box 20, Folder 43)
- Johnson, Robin Mackenzie, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1540 (Box 20, Folder 44)
- Johnson, Sally, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1541 (Box 20, Folder 45)
- Johnston, Peter H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1542 (Box 20, Folder 46)
- Johnstone, Bruce, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1543 (Box 20, Folder 47)
- Johnstone, Bruce D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1544 (Box 20, Folder 48)
- Jones, Alethia, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1545 (Box 20, Folder 49)
- Jones, Christopher C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1546 (Box 20, Folder 50)
- Jones, Gary L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1547 (Box 20, Folder 51)
- Jones, Gary L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1548 (Box 20, Folder 52)
- Jones, Jacquelyn, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1549 (Box 20, Folder 53)
- Jones, Jeffrey J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1550 (Box 20, Folder 54)
- Jones, Jennifer, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1551 (Box 20, Folder 55)
- Jones, Kenneth, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1552 (Box 20, Folder 56)
- Jones, Shirley, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1553 (Box 20, Folder 57)
- Jones, Shirley, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1554 (Box 20, Folder 58)
- Jordan, Bojana Vuyisile, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1555 (Box 20, Folder 59)
- Jorden, Frederick E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1556 (Box 20, Folder 60)
- Jordon, Lucious, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1557 (Box 20, Folder 61)
- Jorgensen, June, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1558 (Box 20, Folder 62)
- Joris, Pierre, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1559 (Box 20, Folder 63)
- Joseph, Deborah, 2001; nam_ua950.003-1560 (Box 20, Folder 64)
- Josey, E.J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1561 (Box 20, Folder 65)
- Juedes, Donald R., 1994-1998; nam_ua950.003-1562 (Box 20, Folder 66)
- Jumpeter, Christine E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1563 (Box 20, Folder 67)
- Juncker, Paul, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1564 (Box 20, Folder 68)
- Jurkowski, Janine M, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1565 (Box 20, Folder 69)
- Jury, Mark, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1566 (Box 20, Folder 70)
- Justeson, John, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1567 (Box 20, Folder 71)
- Kaczor, Sue A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1568 (Box 20, Folder 72)
- Kadlecek, John, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1569 (Box 20, Folder 73)
- Kadlecek, John A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1570 (Box 20, Folder 74)
- Kagan, Richard M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1571 (Box 20, Folder 75)
- Kahalas, Harvey, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1572 (Box 20, Folder 76)
- Kakumba, Dawn V., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1573 (Box 20, Folder 77)
- Kalish, Richard Jerome, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1574 (Box 20, Folder 78)
- Kallman, Howard J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1575 (Box 20, Folder 79)
- Kaloyeros, Alain, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1576 (Box 20, Folder 80)
- Kaloyeros, Alain, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1577 (Box 20, Folder 81)
- Kaloyeros, Alain, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1578 (Box 20, Folder 82)
- Kaloyeros, Alain, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1579 (Box 20, Folder 83)
- Kaloyeros, Alain, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1580 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Kamberelis, George, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1581 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Kanes, Martin, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1582 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Kane, Shirley, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1583 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Kane, Shirley M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1584 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Kaneko, Motohisa, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1585 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Kapechuk, Walter, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1586 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Garcia-Kapelewski, Martha, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1587 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Kanes, Martin, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1588 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Kapur, Deepak, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1589 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Karageorghia, Vassos, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1590 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Karlin, Kenneth D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1591 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Karlson, Karleen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1592 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Karpel, Leon, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1593 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Karpinski, Jakub, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1594 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Karsick, Margaret Barnes, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1595 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Karson, William, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1596 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Karuzan, O. Charles, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1597 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Kashiwase, Yasuji, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1598 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Kastle, Leonard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1599 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Katagiri, Catharine M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1600 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Katz, Daniel J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1601 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Katz, Linda S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1602 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Katz, Linda Steinberg, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1603 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Katz, Melvin L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1604 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Katz, Melvin, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1605 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Katz, Selig H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1606 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Katz, Sydney S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1607 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Katz, William, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1608 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Katz, William A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1609 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Kaufer, David S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1610 (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Kavanagh, Michael, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1611 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Kavanagh, Michael J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1612 (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Kazmierski, Georgiana M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1613 (Box 21, Folder 34)
- Kehe, Zhu, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1614 (Box 21, Folder 35)
- Kekes, John, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1615 (Box 21, Folder 36)
- Keller, Kevin E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1616 (Box 21, Folder 37)
- Keller, William E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1617 (Box 21, Folder 38)
- Kelley, Kathryn, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1618 (Box 21, Folder 39)
- Kellner, Menachem, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1619 (Box 21, Folder 40)
- Kellogg, Ruth, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1620 (Box 21, Folder 41)
- Kelly, Brian V., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1621 (Box 21, Folder 42)
- Kelly, Edward F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1622 (Box 21, Folder 43)
- Kelly, James F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1623 (Box 21, Folder 44)
- Kelly, Piret K, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1624 (Box 21, Folder 45)
- Kelly, Richard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1625 (Box 21, Folder 46)
- Kelly, Richard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1626 (Box 21, Folder 47)
- Kelly, Thomas G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1627 (Box 21, Folder 48)
- Kelly, Thomas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1628 (Box 21, Folder 49)
- Kelsey, Jean, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1629 (Box 21, Folder 50)
- Kemmerer, Frances, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1630 (Box 21, Folder 51)
- Kemmerer, Frances, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1631 (Box 21, Folder 52)
- Kemp, Barbara, 1994; nam_ua950.003-1632 (Box 21, Folder 53)
- Kendall, Kathleen A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1633 (Box 21, Folder 54)
- Kendall, Kathleen E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1634 (Box 21, Folder 55)
- Kendall, Richard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1635 (Box 21, Folder 56)
- Kendall, Richard H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1636 (Box 21, Folder 57)
- Kendra, Christopher - French Department Faculty 1964-1969, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1637 (Box 21, Folder 58)
- Kennedy, William, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1638 (Box 21, Folder 59)
- Kennedy, William, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1639 (Box 21, Folder 60)
- Kennedy, William, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1640 (Box 21, Folder 61)
- Kennedy, William, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1641 (Box 21, Folder 62)
- Kennedy, William, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1642 (Box 21, Folder 63)
- Kenney, Ralph B., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1643 (Box 21, Folder 64)
- Kenny, David George, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1644 (Box 21, Folder 65)
- Keogan, Shonna, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1645 (Box 21, Folder 66)
- Keohane, John J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1646 (Box 21, Folder 67)
- Keough, Brian, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1647 (Box 21, Folder 68)
- Keough, Brian, 2001; nam_ua950.003-1648 (Box 21, Folder 69)
- Keough, Brian, 1999; nam_ua950.003-1649 (Box 21, Folder 70)
- Kern, Douglas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1650 (Box 21, Folder 71)
- Kersten, Christian, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1651 (Box 21, Folder 72)
- Kessler, Jane, 2000; nam_ua950.003-1652 (Box 21, Folder 73)
- Kessler, Martin, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1653 (Box 21, Folder 74)
- Ketterer, James, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1654 (Box 21, Folder 75)
- Kettlewell, Karen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1655 (Box 21, Folder 76)
- Keyomarsi, Khandan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1656 (Box 21, Folder 77)
- Keys, Raymond, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1657 (Box 21, Folder 78)
- Keyser, Daniel, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1658 (Box 21, Folder 79)
- Khwaja, Haider, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1659 (Box 21, Folder 80)
- Kidder, Amy Friedman, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1660 (Box 21, Folder 81)
- Kielt, James P., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1661 (Box 21, Folder 82)
- Kiepper, James J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1662 (Box 21, Folder 83)
- Kiepper, James J., 1964-1992; nam_ua950.003-1663 (Box 21, Folder 84)
- Kifer, Allan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1664 (Box 21, Folder 85)
- Kikuchi, Akio (visiting 1968-69), Undated; nam_ua950.003-1665 (Box 21, Folder 86)
- Kilcullen, Thomas F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1666 (Box 21, Folder 87)
- Kim, Jai S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1667 (Box 21, Folder 88)
- Kim, Jai Soo, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1668 (Box 21, Folder 89)
- Kim, Sung Bok, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1669 (Box 21, Folder 90)
- Kim, Sung Bok, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1670 (Box 21, Folder 91)
- Kim, Sung Bok, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1671 (Box 21, Folder 92)
- Kim, Sung Bok, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1672 (Box 21, Folder 93)
- Kim, Yong Moo, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1673 (Box 21, Folder 94)
- Kimball, John, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1674 (Box 21, Folder 95)
- Kimball, Kenneth R., Jr., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1675 (Box 21, Folder 96)
- Kinal, Terrence W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1676 (Box 21, Folder 97)
- Kinard, Elissa, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1677 (Box 21, Folder 98)
- Kincaid, Lawrence, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1678 (Box 21, Folder 99)
- King, Carolyn, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1679 (Box 21, Folder 100)
- King, James, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1680 (Box 21, Folder 101)
- King, Jonathan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1681 (Box 21, Folder 102)
- King, Robert (chancellor), Undated; nam_ua950.003-1682 (Box 21, Folder 103)
- King, Ryan D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1683 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- King, Tsoo E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1684 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- King, Tsoo E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1685 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- King, Tsoo E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1686 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Kingma, Bruce, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1687 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Kinney, Thomas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1688 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Kinney, Thomas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1689 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Kirk, Russell, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1690 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Kirk, Stuart A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1691 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Kirwin, Arthur Jr., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1692 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Kivlen, Chris, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1693 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Kisseleff, Natalia, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1694 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Kizenko, Nadiezda, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1695 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Klages, Roy Arthur, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1696 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Klein, Alan F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1697 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Klein, Alan F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1698 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Klempner, Irving M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1699 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Klempner, Irving M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1700 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Kleppel, Gary, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1701 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Kleppel, Gary, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1702 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Klima, George, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1703 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Klima, George J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1704 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Kline, David, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1705 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Klopott, R. Beth, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1706 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Klor De Alva, J. Jorge, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1707 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Knapp, Sara D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1708 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Knapp, Sarah, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1709 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Knee, Michael J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1710 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Knight, Christopher J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1711 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Knight-Thomas, Dawn, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1712 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Knoblaugh, Cyril H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1713 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Knoff, Howard M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1714 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Knotts, Walter E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1715 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Knotts, Walter E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1716 (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Knouse, Reno, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1717 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Knuth, Kevin, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1718 (Box 22, Folder 36)
- Ko, Hai-Ping, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1719 (Box 22, Folder 37)
- Koban, Charles, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1720 (Box 22, Folder 38)
- Kobrin, David, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1721 (Box 22, Folder 39)
- Koelmel, John (Jack), Undated; nam_ua950.003-1722 (Box 22, Folder 40)
- Koerner, Charlotte W., 1980; nam_ua950.003-1723 (Box 22, Folder 41)
- Koff, Robert H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1724 (Box 22, Folder 42)
- Kolb, Lawrence, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1725 (Box 22, Folder 43)
- Kolesoff, Valerian F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1726 (Box 22, Folder 44)
- Kolmin, Frank W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1727 (Box 22, Folder 45)
- Komisar, Jerome, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1728 (Box 22, Folder 46)
- Kopf, Frank A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1729 (Box 22, Folder 47)
- Kopka, Lynn M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1730 (Box 22, Folder 48)
- Kopka, Lynn M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1731 (Box 22, Folder 49)
- Koplow, Amy H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1732 (Box 22, Folder 50)
- Kopp, Steve, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1733 (Box 22, Folder 51)
- Kopp, Rick, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1734 (Box 22, Folder 52)
- Korenblum, Boris, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1735 (Box 22, Folder 53)
- Korenblum, Boris, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1736 (Box 22, Folder 54)
- Koseloff, Valerian F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1737 (Box 22, Folder 55)
- Koslowski, Rey, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1738 (Box 22, Folder 56)
- Kotval, Jeroo S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1739 (Box 22, Folder 57)
- Kotval, Jeroo S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1740 (Box 22, Folder 58)
- Kouba, Vicky, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1741 (Box 22, Folder 59)
- Kowalchyk, John J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1742 (Box 22, Folder 60)
- Krahn, Mary L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1743 (Box 22, Folder 61)
- Kranich, Laurence Joel, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1744 (Box 22, Folder 62)